for July 19, 2021 and put the invocation by Director of Norse Campus Ministries Mr.
Steve Watson.
It's athletes.
It's a gorgeous group on campus this summer we have 125 football players that are taking
six hours of summer school and here you work out.
I'm brought with us on perspective and then one quarterback just going to press out the
chair running your boat over there.
Mary Olsen is a student from Utah with the Navy transferred in here, we'll be our quarterback
district.
We're optimistic for a great year and he's a big part of the optimism and we'll build our
one winning running streak.
That's really wonderful.
That's a pretty come witness and spread it to my parents.
Thank you guys very much.
Thank you so much for allowing us to come together, fellowship, and one another.
Thank you for giving us the blessings that we take for granted every single day.
Lord, I pray for this council, I pray for the mayor, pray for the attorneys, Lord, pray
for the citizens of my amor.
Please cover your hand over all of us, Mr. Solver, we love you, and you just know I pray.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the five of the United States of America and to the Republic for which
it stands one nation under your eye, individual with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Welcome to my amor.
Look forward to watching the play.
Thank you.
Well, wait just a second.
She's going to hand out the copies of the agenda, sir, by the name of the copy of it.
And I'm going to line on four public input on scheduled personal parentsus, five consent
agenda.
Staff recommends we approve by them six through eight.
So, say more.
So moved.
Second.
Davis?
Hi.
Number.
Parker.
Hi.
Nine.
The Pre-GRA legal claims.
Maurice.
Mr. Mayor, these invoices that are before you day,
are for the services performed in May,
by DWT.
Little Stratton.
In Petrotech.
Per, existing contract, previously approved by the Council.
Any questions or concerns about those?
Where are those pertain to, like,
so the bulk of that work done in May?
It was to follow up to the GRDA Technical Conference.
And we had working with DWT and Tehrotech,
they run a technical brief response to that evaluation,
identifying some of the Council's comments.
They have been made.
I think, Council member, you step.
Had some input during the conference.
And that was offered into legal briefing.
That was named submitted to GRDA.
How much is that for?
So combined.
There was about $44,853.
That includes legal fees and hydraulic engineering fees
from Petrotech.
About that 44.
The breakdown was about 24,000.
It was the technical aspect of it.
And then 16,000 and 3,000.
The legal fees.
I'll make a motion.
I'll second.
Don't hold.
Hi.
Davis.
Parker?
Hi.
Ten.
Approved also the Master Agreement.
Work Order 2022-1 for General City Engineering Services.
I don't see you shall.
No.
Mr. Mayor, we are going to ask that we push that to a future meeting.
We had a couple of complications with our technology and getting that contract and distributed.
You know, available to Council members.
And we want to make sure that we, you know, don't get it out.
But we get it out early enough so that everyone's got time to review it.
So we just want to strike that one for today and we'll bring it back to you.
I'll ask you a question on that.
Good morning.
I've seen it when it's a agreement in 2016.
And it all's done.
Yes.
Since it has been put out together with any other engineers in the area.
Any other firms to offer us the same services, also offers us.
Since I have new, I'm going to defer to legal.
I see.
And I'm looking to Tyler.
He is telling me that.
So there's probably just been the amendments that we've seen.
Yeah.
The amendments to the contract, but not rebid.
So is that something that we can look into to make sure we're getting best paying for
our budget.
So there's other qualified firms after that.
Does the same thing also does in the area?
Yeah.
I can tell you that I am a huge fan of the bidding process.
Believe it or not.
Being a long time state employee.
I believe in the competitive process.
And I will certainly evaluate that and get back to council.
Any pros, cons to that in this case.
I don't want to say definitely.
I'm always a fan.
So let us see what that would be like.
Make sure there's not a timing issue.
Then we'll get back.
All right.
Number 11.
We're also going to table.
That takes us number 12 staff reports.
Any questions on those?
13.
Another new business of any, which is a risen.
Supposing of this agenda.
14.
Trustee community announcements.
15.
Thank you.
Make motion.
It's like...
December?
All right.
May this?
Thank you.